<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Philosopher of Language</title>
    <link>https://grammatician.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Philosopher of Language</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 09:46:35 +1200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://grammatician.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Programming</title>
      <link>https://grammatician.github.io/post/programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 09:46:35 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://grammatician.github.io/post/programming/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been programming in C++ and I am really happy with the language. Function signatures form their own grammar, and I rely heavily on this for calculation
I rely heavely on reading funciton declarations. Having them in header files seperated from their definitions, makes C++ easier to read than C# where you have to wade through the definitions to read the signature.
Without static typing, languages like Python are totally incomprehensible to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Blog&#39;s Premise</title>
      <link>https://grammatician.github.io/post/premise/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://grammatician.github.io/post/premise/</guid>
      <description>Every field has it&amp;rsquo;s own unique grammar. These grammars can be noun orientated or verb orientated. Verb orientated grammers are actionable, noun grammars are not, and it is interesting to think about why the Teleology demands a particular grammars orientation.
Classical education taught Rhetorical Devices. These are set pieces that can be performed by a writer. However, modernity has all but abandoned this tradition. Linguists merely seek to describe, and language educaters have a distaste for the objective and wallow in the subjective.
The purpose of this blog is to develop a new grammar for language, finding a vocabulary that is verb orientated.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
